Inventory of the Carter Family Papers 1667-1862
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
- People Files, 1667-1862. (Folder 1-102)
  - Carter, (Robert W.) 1792-1861; 1803-1862, n.d. (Folder 20-101)
    - Letters, 1803-1861. (Folder 20-50)
      - Letters, 1855., items. (Folder 42)
        - William T. Jesse, at Nuttsville, [Lancaster County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, 2 May 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - William B. Beverley, at Blandfield, [Essex County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 6 May 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - Wat H. Tyler, at Wilton, to [Robert W. Carter], 12 May 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - William N. Ward, at Bladensfield, [Richmond County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, 16 May 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - William H. Richardson, at Richmond, to Col. R. W. Carter, 23 May 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - William T. Jesse, at Nuttsville, [Lancaster County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, 24 May 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - S. F. Livingston, at Kinsale, [Westmoreland County], Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, 30 May 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - William N. Ward, at Bladensfield, [Richmond County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 2 June 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - Robert W. Carter to [S. F.] Livingstone, 4 June 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - R. W. C[arter] to Edward Tayloe, 10 June 1855., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 42)
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 12 June 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, 14 June 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - G. H. VanNess, at Tappahannock, to Col. R. W. Carter, 15 June 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - [Robert W. Carter] to [?] Lomax, 16 June 1855., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 42)
        - R. S. Hipkins, at Tappahannock, to [Robert W. Carter], 19 June 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - R. E. Scott, at Oakwood, [Fauquier County], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Virginia, 28 June 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - J. B. Ficklen, at Falmouth, [Stafford County], to R. W. Carter, 29 June 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - J. A. Carter, at Crednal, to Robert [W. Carter], 10 July 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, 10 July 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - F. W. Pendleton, at Warsaw, Virginia, to Col. [R. W. Carter], 17 July 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - G. H. Dobyns, at Tappahannock, to Col. R. W. Carter, 7 Aug 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - Dennard Phillips, at Baltimore, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, 8 Aug 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - John W. Lyell, at Virginia Military Institute, [Lexington, Virginia], to Col. Carter, 11 Aug 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - R. H. Lyell, at Farnham Church, [Richmond County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 15 Aug 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - F. W. Pendleton, at Warsaw, Virginia, to [Robert W. Carter], 21 Aug 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, at Fredericksburg, 24 Aug 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - Thomas Parker, at Montross, [Westmoreland County], to [Robert W. Carter], 28 Aug 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, at Fredericksburg, 31 Aug 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - William N. Ward, at Bladensfield, [Richmond County], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 3 Sept 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - E. Poinsett Tayloe, at Powhatan, [King George County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 13 Sept 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Fredericksburg, 26 Oct 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - H. P. F. King to Col. Robert Carter, 2 Nov 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - Thomas Parker, at Montross, [Westmoreland County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, 8 Nov 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - J. Brown, Jr., at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw P.O., 9 Nov 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - America Anthony, Hanover County, to [Robert W. Carter], 10 Dec 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 11 Dec 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - Alexander Lang, at Fredericksburg, to [Robert W.] Carter, 17 Dec 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - J. S. Boughton, at Tappahannock, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 21 Dec 1855., 1 item. (Folder 42)
        - R. W. C[arter] to James Pare, 24 Dec 1855., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 42)
      - Letters, 1856. (Folder 43)
        - J. Minor, [agent], Franklin Fire Insurance Company of Philadelphia, at Fredericksburg, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 1 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - B. R. Wellford, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 1 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
          Note: A statement of account is added to this letter.
        - William D. Garland to Col. Robert W. Carter, 7 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - William T. Harris, at Warsaw, to Col. R. W. Carter, Richmond County, 7 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to R. W. Carter, 10 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 14 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - R. E. Scott, at Oakwood, [Fauquier County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 16 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 22 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - E. C. Edwards, at Warsaw, [Richmond County], to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 29 Jan 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - James Dickenson to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 12 Feb 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, at Sabine Hall, 13 Feb 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
          Enclosure: An extract from the Report of the Executive Committee of the Rappahannock River Agricultural Society.
        - J. Brown, Jr., at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Warsaw P. O., Virginia, 15 Feb 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Wellford Eastham & Co., at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw P. O., 15 Feb 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - B[laden] T. Tayloe, at Powhatan, [King George County], to Robert W. Carter, 23 Feb 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - John S. Devenport, Northumberland County, to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 8 March 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 10 March 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - W. H. Roy, at Green Plains, [Gloucester County], to Col. Robert Carter, at Sabine Hall, 24 March 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - W. M. Fauntleroy to Col. R. W. Carter, 4 April 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - W. T. Harris to Col. Robert W. Carter, 5 April 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 12 April 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - W. M. Fauntleroy to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 13 April 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - J. A. Carter, at Crednal, to Robert [W. Carter], 6 May 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - William T. Jesse, at Nuttsville, [Lancaster County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, 29 May 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - R. E. Scott to Col. R. W. Carter, 30 May 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - William H. Coffin to Col. R. W. Carter, [May 1856.], 1 item. (Folder 43)
          Enclosure: Certificate of election of Robert W. Carter as a lay delegate to the convention of the Protestant Episcopal Church in the Diocese of Virginia.
        - James W. Hipkins, at Durrettsville, to Col. Carter, 6 June 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Francis B. Jones, at Carysbrooke, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 10 June 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - J. R. Lowry to Col. Carter, 28 June 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Robert Y. Conrad, at Winchester, to Col. Robert Carter, 30 June 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, at Sabine Hall, 14 July 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - J. D. B. DeBow, at Washington, D. C., to [Robert W. Carter], 20 Aug 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - James H. Barney, at Baltimore, to Robert W. Carter, 1 Sept 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Charles Marshall, at Baltimore, to Col. R. W. Carter, 2 Oct 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - P. T. Lomax to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 9 Oct 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - John M. Brockenbrough, at Island, [Richmond County], to [Robert W. Carter], 10 Oct 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - George W. Munford, at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, Richmond County, 10 Oct 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Robert Howard, at Richmond, to [Robert W. Carter], 3 Nov 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Thomas B. Bigger, postmaster, at Richmond, Virginia, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Virginia, 17 Nov 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - P. A. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, 6 Dec 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - John Critcher, at Bankton, to [Robert W. Carter], 26 Dec 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - J. B. Ficklen, at Falmouth, [Stafford County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 26 Dec 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - E. R. Pullen to Col. Robert W. Carter, 27 Dec 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - J. S. Boughton, at Tappahannock, to Col. R. W. Carter, 29 Dec 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
        - Edward C. Marshall to [Robert W. Carter], 1856., 1 item. (Folder 43)
      - Letters, 1857. (Folder 44)
        - Robert Y. Conrad, at Winchester, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 2 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Francis B. Jones, at Carysbrooke, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 2 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - F. W. Pendleton to Col. Carter, 2 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - William H. Coffin, at Durrettsville, to R. W. Carter, 3 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - J. R. Jeffries to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 9 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - J. A. Carter, at Sharrawa[?], to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 11 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
          Postmarked Upperville, Virginia.
        - R. W Carter, at Sabine Hall, to F. Slaughter, 13 Jan 1857., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 44)
        - J. M. Mason, at Washington, to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 14 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - J. S. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, to Col. [Robert W. Carter], 15 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - R. L. T. Beale, at Cabinford, to Col. [Robert W. Carter], 16 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to R. W. Carter, 16 Jan 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
          Note: A copy of Col. R. W. Carter's reply is filed with this letter.
        - E. Conway, at Fredericksburg, to R. W. Carter, 13 Feb 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Samuel Gresham, at Lancaster Court House, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 13 Feb 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - J. Harrison Kelly, at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, 16 Feb 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 16 Feb 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - [Robert W. Carter] to B[enjamin] O[gle] Tayloe, 19 Feb 1857., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 44)
        - Gordon Forbes, at Sandy Point, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 21 Feb 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Francis B. Jones, at Carysbrooke, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 21 Feb 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Two letters written on the same page, Feb - March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
          Two letters written on the same page: William T. Harris, at Warsaw, to Col. Carter, 24 Feb 1857.
          R. W. C[arter] to [William T. Harris], 6 March 1857.
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. R. W Carter, at Sabine Hall, 24 Feb 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - J. R. Jeffries, at Warsaw, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 26 Feb 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - R. S. Hipkins, at Tappahannock, to [Robert W. Carter], 4 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Edmund Withers, at Lancaster Court House, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, 6 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Robert Y. Conrad, at Winchester, to Col. R. W. Carter, 7 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - John Glenn, at Baltimore, to Robert W. Carter. 13 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - P. A. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Warsaw P.O., Richmond County, 13 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, Alabama, to Col. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 21 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Thomas Yerby, at Fredericksburg, to [Robert W. Carter], 21 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - William T. Jesse, at Nuttsville, [Lancaster County], to Col. Robert W. Carter, 23 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Joshua L. Boughton, at Tappahannock, to Col. R. W. Carter, 24 March 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - John M. Siegfried, at Easton, Pennsylvania, to Robert Carter, 20 April 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 20 April 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 23 April 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
          Enclosure: Account of E. T. Tayloe with Robert W. Carter, 1853-1854.
        - W. A. Wright, at Tappahannock, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 25 April 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - R. W. C[arter] to [Benjamin Ogle Tayloe], 29 April 1857., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 44)
        - Carey J[?] Hall, at Farnham, [Richmond County], to [Robert W. Carter], 29 April 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 4 May 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - P. A. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, 7 May 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 11 May 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - C. Newcomb to Col. R. W. Carter, 14 May 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - J. C. Moncure, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 23 May 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - George W. Munford, at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Virginia, 4 June 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - J. R. Jeffries to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 19 Aug 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - James Cooke & Co., at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter. Richmond County, Virginia, 1 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Col. [Robert W. Carter], 5 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - James B. Northern, at Warsaw, Virginia, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 6 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. Robert W Carter, at Sabine Hall, 11 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Col. [Robert W. Carter], 11 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Edward C. Marshall, at Markham, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 13 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Coleman Smith, at Stevensville, [King and Queen County], to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 19 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 19 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Edwin Goffigon, at Capeville, [Northampton County], to Robert W. Carter, 26 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - C. Smith, at Stevensville, [King and Queen County], to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 31 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
          Enclosure: Copy of a letter written by Elias Harroll, a slave, to a negro friend.
        - Coleman Smith, at Stevensville, [King and Queen County], to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 31 Oct 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Henry Lyell, at Farnham Church, [Richmond County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 5 Nov 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - R. S. Hipkins, at Tappahannock, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 12 Nov 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Thomas S. Waugh, at Tappahannock, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 28 Nov 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Joshua L. Boughton, at Tappahannock, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Richmond, 18 Dec 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - J. R. Jeffries, at Warsaw, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond City, 19 Dec 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - Thomas S. Waugh, at Tappahannock, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 22 Dec 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
        - G. W. Lewis, at Claymont, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 24 Dec 1857., 1 item. (Folder 44)
      - Letters, 1858. (Folder 45)
        - Thomas M. Arnest, at Nomony Hall, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 8 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - J. R Jeffries to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond City, Virginia, Postmarked 8 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Francis B. Jones, at Carysbrooke, to Col. Robert W Carter, 14 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - E. C. Edwards, at Warsaw, to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 19 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Lyne Shackleford, at Warsaw, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Richmond, 19 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - F. W. Pendleton, at Warsaw, Virginia, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 22 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - William Harding, at Heathsville, [Northumberland County], Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, 25 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Ann M. Lemoine, at Oakland, near Durrettsville P. O., to Col. Carter, 25 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - J. R. Lowry to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 26 Jan 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Robert Y. Conrad, at Winchester, to Col. R. W. Carter, 11 Feb 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - George B. Scott, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 11 Feb 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - William A. Harrison, at Clarksburg, [Harrison County], Virginia, to [Robert W. Carter], 12 Feb 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - R. S. Hipkins, at Tappahannock, to Col. Robert W Carter, 5 March 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - B[laden] T. Tayloe, at Powhatan, [King George County], to R. W. Carter, at Richmond, Virginia, 13 March 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - John W. Phillips to Col. Robert W. Carter, 22 March 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - R. W. C[arter], Richmond County, Virginia, to G. W. Munford, at Richmond, Virginia, 17 May 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Matilda A. Jeffries, at The Glebe, to Col. Carter, 3 June 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - J. C. Moncure, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 14 June 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Girard House, [Philadelphia?], to Col. R. W Carter, at Sabine Hall, 23 June 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 23 July 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - [?] Bloxton, at Poplar Hill, to Col. R. Carter, at Fredericksburg, Spottsylvania [County], 30 July 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - J. R. Lowry to Col. Carter, 30 July 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Robert Mayo, Jr., at Hague, [Westmoreland County], to Col. R. W. Carter, 4 Aug 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, 15 Aug 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Benjamin Ogle Tayloe, at Washington, to Col. Carter, 4 Sept 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Thomas D. Mutter, at Philadelphia, to Col. Carter, 4 Oct 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - H. Miller, at Warsaw, to Col. [Robert W.] Carter, 22 Oct 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - John P. McGuire, at Howard Theological Seminary P. O., Fairfax County, Virginia, 3 Nov 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Edward C. Marshall, at Markham, to Robert W. Carter, 5 Nov 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Howard Miller, at Warsaw, to Col. R. W. Carter, 6 Nov 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Thomas S. Waugh, at Tappahannock, Virginia, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 20 Nov 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - C[harles] C[arter] Lee, at Five Creeks, Powhatan [County], to Robert [W. Carter], 24 Nov 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - George W. Clark, at Norwich, Connecticut, to Robert Carter, 27 Nov 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - Mary S. Branham, at Rose Hill, Richmond County, Virginia, to Col. Carter, 13 Dec 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
        - R. W. C[arter] to G. Lewis, 15 Dec 1858., 1 item. Copy. (Folder 45)
        - Joshua L. Boughton, at Tappahannock, to R. W. Carter, 27 Dec 1858., 1 item. (Folder 45)
      - Letters, 1859. (Folder 46)
        - Howard Miller, at Warsaw, to Col. Robert W Carter, at Sabine Hall, 1 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - John R. Thompson, at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, near Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 1 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
          Enclosure: C[harles] C[arter] Lee, at Richmond, to Col. R. W. Carter, 1 Jan 1859.
        - Andrew Fisher, at Warsaw, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 4 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - Edward L. Fant, at Warrenton, Virginia, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 7 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
          Enclosure: A sample of merino wool.
        - B. R. Wellford, at Richmond, to Col. Robert W. Carter, 15 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - J. S. Wellford, at Fredericksburg, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 18 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - J. Warren Slaughter, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, Richmond County, 27 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Richmond, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 27 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - Edward L. Fant, at Warrenton, Virginia, to Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, Richmond County, Virginia, 28 Jan 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - A. T. Caperton, at Union, Monroe County, Virginia, to Col. [Robert W. Carter], 7 Feb 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Richmond, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 10 Feb 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - J. Warren Slaughter, at Fredericksburg, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 24 Feb 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - William N. Ward, Jr., at Bladensfield, [Richmond County], Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 3 March 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - John W. Phillips to Col. R. W. Carter, 12 March 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - A. N. Wellford, at Richmond, Virginia, to Col. R. W Carter, at Sabine - Hall, 17 March 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - Richard B. Mitchell, at Ridgefield, to Col. Robert W. Carter, at Warsaw, 23 March 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - Waller R. Staples, at Christiansburg, [Montgomery County] to [Robert W. Carter], 25 March 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
        - J. C. Shields, for the State Central Committee, [Whig Party], at Richmond, to Robert W. Carter, 28 March 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)
          Enclosure: Printed circular letter from R. T. Daniel, chairman, State Central Committee, Richmond, Virginia, 23 Feb 1859.
        - A. N. Wellford, at Richmond, Virginia, to Col. R. W. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 28 March 1859., 1 item. Mutilated. (Folder 46)
        - Edward T. Tayloe, at Powhatan Hill, [King George County], to Col. Carter, at Sabine Hall, 14 April 1859., 1 item. (Folder 46)